at the time which was just helping
people at various locations throughout
my seven plus year uh career in security
and bodyguard work where I actually
sustained three serious concussions with
a total of 15 whoa and
[Music]
[Applause]
well hello there folks um I am super
excited for today uh welcome to the
hustle Zone uh the world's first living
documentary um what does that mean well
we are um we we compile um interviews of
people um talking about their
experiences and their stories and and
and whatnot um we're a living
documentary because we you know our
videos are recorded live like all of the
interviews that we do are recorded live
um you know and we fact check
live um and our website is just a
compilation of all these uh interviews
talking about entrepreneurship so you
know we're claiming we're the first
living documentary and um you know I'm
your host Ryan Perez owner and founder
of bowai creative you guys can check us
out we are we are a website company that
does
more so we build websites but we build
online businesses so you definitely want
to check out botc creative.com to see
what we're all about and I just launched
new business branding
gy um branding gy is a uh um is a
company that uh does unlimited graphic
design so I'm super excited about
that um and then uh and then the hustle
Zone if you guys check out hustle
zone.com and uh we are the world's first
living documentary so you guys can check
out this interview that I'm going to be
doing with um Mr Dave Matthew bodies
with be heroes formerly known as
bodyguards United uh so I'm super
excited to have him as a guest so folks
uh how are you guys doing today um I'm
going to ask you all to
um I'm going to ask you all to share
this uh this interview today so I'm just
going to do what I normally do at the
very beginning of it oh I hear some
feedback um I'm going to share this to
the groups that I share to get some more
visibility so let's take this
time let's take this time to share to to
other people within our our networks
because you know what sharing is
caring and um so I'm going to just I'm
just doing it right now so live talk
Nation we're going to share it to them
because they're great people over
there okay perfect and then I'm going to
share this to
podcast um video
podcasting and then I'm going to take a
look at who's in the room
so um so
[Music]
podcast perfect so I've shared I'm ready
to go uh let's go to let's see here G to
log into my Facebook to see who is on
the live right now
so it always takes some time
to log into this thing because it
doesn't always
work but I want to be able to bring your
guys' comments on the
screen
oops so how's everybody doing today how
was your Thanksgiving please put the
comments uh
below and then hopefully we can put it
on screen for you
okay one more second just trying to log
in Hustle
zone. okay perfect we are in so I'm
going to just see if we can grab the
comments and put them on the screen if
not that's okay I'll just read your
comments if uh if that oh we do got some
people in here so we have Dave in in the
house so let's uh uh and he's actually
in in he's actually in in the house but
uh let's uh put the comments up here so
we got
Anna uh Anna hi Anna how are you
doing and um and then obviously Our
Guest has said hey
everybody thanks for tuning in so let's
talk about our guests a little bit I've
known Dave for quite some time we went
to um elementary school
together and um you know I do remember
his face uh because there was a picture
of his face you know he put a baby
picture and I'm like oh I remember that
kid
um but yeah we've known each other for
for quite some time we were we're
putting back into each other's lives um
you know uh probably I would say about
four years ago uh when we were sitting
on an anti-racism
thing we were supposed to be on the news
or what what have you with my friend uh
uh Sunday ommani and uh we kind of grew
a relationship because he was doing
stuff for the kids and you know my past
I was doing youth work um and getting
out to the youth and and talking to them
about anti-bullying and whatnot and he
was kind of doing the same thing and and
now that I don't do it you know I wanted
to kind of support someone that did do
it so you know Dave was on the show
before he was one of the first guests
that we have on the show but we're not
airing his interview because you know
you know there's just a lot of um
changes that we've done to the show so
kind of wanted to roll out the red
carpet for him and
um um and and to to get things moving
along so uh uh Anna says Thanksgiving
was awesome had lunch um in a castle
with family in a castle holy moly uh
that's that's awesome so
uh I want to eat in the castle Jesus uh
so now folks before we get into our show
today um I want to to tell you that you
know hustle Zone TV we have a GoFundMe
campaign so if you go to ww.
gofundme.com
hustle zone. or hyen TV when you go
there we're we're asking we're we're
looking to raise money um to build the
hustle Zone um to make it into what we
we have had envisioned for this project
to be um 50% of which and I'll show you
the the breakdown in a few seconds but
the reason why we're doing this because
we want to offer free entertainment free
edutainment for people um to learn about
building businesses becoming
entrepreneurs through the stories of of
people like my guest and you know also
having people come on and and and
creating um educational content uh
because that's the thing it's like you
know there's there's so much barriers to
to to entry when it comes to education
and we want this this platform this
documentary to be forever free so that
people can get access to it but in order
in order for it to be free we would need
you know your support so I'm going to
show you here
um what we're all about so our our four
main objectives is that we document
Stories We want to offer free education
we want to develop F future
entrepreneurs and we want to create
honest content and uh you know we we
want you guys to fact check us and we'll
put your your your comments on the
screen you know which will be one of the
first uh factchecking uh live streams
where people are kind of focused on
making sure that the education and the
materials that we put on the screen are
the correct materials because sometimes
I'm not always right and that's why we
we want you guys to participate um so uh
I'm going to show you guys our breakdown
here of you know where our funds will go
so you know uh 15 uh 50% it's not 51%
that's a a typo 50 50 uh 50% of our
funds will go into
um uh hiring employees writers and
whatnot because they're not cheap I mean
our guest has done writing for us as
well and you know every time you know if
we have to hire him we want to pay him
so you know that's where all that money
will go
and also um so and then we want to do
travel we want to get lawyers and
whatnot just to make sure that we
protect the Integrity of the brand um 5%
admin cost and then the other 15% will
be for Tech so you know that's where the
money will go again you guys can go to
um you know you can go to hustle Zone um
via GoFundMe and um it will break down
all the awards and and the stuff that
you get when you make your contributions
so let's go back to the comments here
before we get started
um hold on one second this this comment
is actually pretty pretty long uh
so Anna says uh um
Belhurst oh I don't know where that
comment went I think it just took long
to to load up Belhurst Castle is a
Geneva New York their Instagram is good
the owner of the castle came by to the
table and make sure that everything was
good that's awesome that's awesome so
you know and then she says good goals
all right so let's get started so this
is uh we're going to introduce to you
again on the hustle Zone he's no
stranger to us in Bow TI creative and
and whatnot but want you guys to um give
me a virtual Round of Applause for Mr
Dave body how are you doing Dave hold on
one second here so there we go there you
are how are you doing
Dave I'm fantastic how are you I'm doing
great I'm doing great so welcome to the
hustle Zone again are you excited I'm
excited to do this all over as the
first not the level it's now I'm very
excited to see
Alles good job awesome so we're not
getting audio coming in so just give me
a few seconds while we figure out why
and then we're going to do this again so
um and thank God we're we edit our
videos afterwards so uh so hi Dave how
are you doing I'm fantastic how are you
I'm doing I'm doing great so are you
excited to be on the hustle zone I'm
excited for round two the first time we
did this was oh geez over a year ago and
as you said it was it was good but I'm
glad to see all all the amazing changes
so far it looks really really good great
production Ryan good job oh thank you
and and uh I mean you've done some
you've done some great you've done some
great things um you know uh you've done
some some great things with be heroes
and and bodyguards United like you know
and then you've done great things for
other people so tell us a little bit
about what you've been up to oh yeah for
sure so bodyguards and a went through a
branding change on my birthday actually
courtesy of be uh buai creative we de
debuted a new logo and with that I
wanted to take a new Direction and what
I realized was that there wasn't really
much social media involvement for groups
that's was focused and targeted for
youth so I wanted to create a community
that was basically just mainly focused
on finding these talented and passionate
youths and just acknowledging them and
praising them for their all their hard
work because I've learned through my
research ever since I began coaching
youth that youths are inspired
drastically by by fellow youths more
than they are adults because when adults
speak to them they feel like they're
being preached to or spoken down to and
whatnot but I found what when teenagers
and youth are the inspirational source
for other youth it has tremendous
results so therefore we've now increased
to 66 b Heroes and 27 B hero ambassadors
and we're building a huge Community
online that's amazing that's that's
that's awesome and uh um Anna Anna
says Applause so you know great great
job on that and yeah you know like
you're right I I think that youth like
and you know and I see with my son
because with all the with all the stuff
that I do um you know my son is not
really inspired with what I do but he's
inspired by guava juice and he's
inspired by danant TDM and all these
different guys that are out there and he
likes to watch you know all the all the
movies that I think is corny he loves to
watch those corny movies because they
have kids in them and um you know so
he's definitely inspired by you know his
generation
and um you know so we have to encourage
people encourage you to come together
but also give them the plateau um and
the environment for them to thrive in
and and that's what you've been
definitely doing and uh we have uh Shan
Malon in the house how are you doing
Sean do you know Shan Dave yeah Sean is
actually the president of teens of
America and teens of America radio
network who I collaborated with the last
six months and has given an amazing
platform for being heres live awesome
awesome that's great well uh nice to
meet you Sean and so let's get let's get
into it so you know you should know our
our uh our platform by now Dave but um
you know uh but for all those who don't
know there's one question that we ask
you and um that question is what is your
story so tell us a little like tell us
you know how did you get here before the
success and I think you were the one
that had one of our earlier slogans
um you had said uh um you we what what
was the earlier slogans it was the story
behind The Glory right and oh yeah so
that was I we didn't we did end up using
it later because a lot of the the
functions of bch creative and hustle
Zone have changed but still you know you
know give us the story behind The Glory
like you know let us know um how you got
here yeah for sure I was I actually
created the concept and the idea of be a
Community while in my brain injury rehab
for my 15th severe concussion where I
got diagnosed with permanent brain
damage that affects my vision and my
comprehension level and with that it
also increased many symptoms with my
ADHD and as a result of all that I had
to retire from active security which was
my passion at the time which was just
helping people at various locations
throughout my seven plus year uh career
and security and bodyguard work where I
actually sustained three serious
concussions with a total of 15 whoa and
when I had to retire from security and
bodyguard work I felt like I lost a huge
part of me which was access to helping
kids because when I worked at Mara mall
for four years I had a huge involvement
with helping kids that were involved in
prostitution gangs and drugs and
depression so much more that when I lost
the element of security and bodyguard
work I felt like I lost a huge part of
me so I decided that I wanted to create
something that would be a community base
towards just recognizing and
acknowledging
and what happened was I started sharing
my story with my own personal experience
with bullying and depression of 16 years
and bound to Suicide three times and I
realized that when I shared my story it
actually built a following to share
their story so in reality like I
realized that the best way to heal was
to help others heal with you so I
designed to Be Your Heroes to be a big
community of just youths that looked to
adults and fellow youths that have been
through what they're going through and
then I realized that when I was doing
research that social media was one of
the major Avenues in which youth were
experiencing abuse assault and
harassment and I figured well I needed
to create a community that would be
social media focused to allow these
youth a place to
go now um why get into all of this
though like you know it's easy to be
like you know I was inspired to you know
help out the youth but what was the
major you know what was the thing that
kind of pushed you over the Edge what
was the event in your life that kind of
you know put uh um things into
perspective for you yeah I I actually
wrote about it on my medium account
called a simple gester where I had a
female teenager that was caught for
stealing a Dollarama and when I walked
into the office to give her her band
notice and to uh basically explain what
it meant I realized that she was just
physically shaken up so I asked her just
one simple question was what's wrong
what's going on and she told me that she
was was recently uh pregnant and her
parents on the street and she had
nowhere to go so her survival method of
fight or flight kicked in the fight and
which result in her stealing and I just
felt terrible for her so off you know
off scene away from fellow police
officers and security officers I gave
her $20 bill and I said listen this is
not much but it's all I can do to help
you out right now and then a year later
or actually a year and some later she
saw me again and she gave me some roses
and gave me a hug and said that because
of my simple gesture she changed her
life around and she graduated high
school and was a in college she gave
birth to a beautiful baby that was
healthy her her family actually took her
back in just because I took the
initiative to say what's wrong and give
her a situation to you know be able to
speak with what was happening to her
that's where I really realized how
important a simple gesture can be for
just
everyone now we have uh in the comments
section here uh Chrystal day Chief uh a
mutual friend of ours um that has been a
great supporter of what you've been
doing and you've been a supporter of of
of her family and and what they've been
doing uh she says youth can relate to
other youth that's why platforms like
Instagram are so um so popular musically
and so on yeah and I'm so out of touch
like I thought I was like instagam
Instagram King I was a rapper but now
I'm old so I I don't even know like half
the things that the youth are doing
they're just you know rapidly changing
and and getting into all kinds of things
of of expressing themselves artistically
and I think it's great and and Dave you
and I had had conversations offline of
of Youth just getting um you know
starting their own businesses starting
you know social media marketing and and
and whatnot so empowering themselves to
even to another level 17year old you
were mentioning what who was the 17
17year old that was uh you know now a
multi-millionaire oh I think he's Frozen
so that's okay hold on one second are we
good now yeah we are good now uh you
were frozen there for a second so let me
just pull yeah on my end it was saying
that you're uh it was showing that your
your your signal length was down in the
red and that's when it started acting up
yeah that's crazy that's okay technology
right yeah technology so folks we we are
back but you know that's why we build
those uh that's why we build those
contingencies because uh you know just
in case any of that stuff happens uh but
yeah so we were talking about the
17-year-old millionaire um who is that
17-year-old millionaire that was uh um
that you were talking about earlier oh
yeah his name is Casey Adams with a c
he's actually a b hero and a good friend
of mine he just appeared in Huffington
Post about an article that he's now a
multi- uh a business owner for a
multi-million dollar company that he
built basically himself with a lot of
great connections that's amazing that's
amazing so now you got some um you got
some uh uh uh I guess um some projects
in the works so you have a film project
that you're working on can you tell us a
little bit about
that yeah actually I I'll just attack Tu
bir one stone basically my friend Dustin
and I who's a Dustin's an LA director uh
Dustin kinging him and I
created a short film called photographic
memory which casted Dominique Swain and
Disney Channel's Mia tolero and we're
now in the North American Film circuit
we made our debut and Premiere at the wi
International Film Festival on October
20th and on October 22nd we won our
first best short film award and we're
coming into the season now where we're
going to be making some huge
announcements because we had to wait for
the uh the announcements from the short
film uh festivals themselves so we're
basically just waiting for what we can
announce and when but we have some huge
announcers coming up and on top of that
we're also developing our second short
film as we speak which will be in
regards to paranoia and
PTSD that's crazy that's I I think
that's amazing you know that you that
you've because you've been you've been
working on this for many years right um
and then you've been in the movie
industry um uh you know doing extra work
and and whatnot and then writing for for
different you know projects and and
whatnot so how are you how are you
feeling now to have this all come into
fruition honestly it's a it's a huge
confidence booster because all through
Junior High and high school I had this
natural attention towards the
entertainment industry but I didn't have
the confidence level to actually pursue
it so once I got the confidence level to
pursue it and I went just all gung-ho on
it it's been a lot of hard work like
photographic memory took us eight months
to write and it went through a lot of
changes a lot of uh storyline Direction
changes because at first my creativity
went through the roof and I realized
wait we had to write a film that was
financially logical so I had to take a
lot about my you know creativity back
but it worked out very well I started
off just doing background work um in the
acting aspect however I made my debut as
a producer with the Sunday andani show
on Sha TV where I produced that TV show
for two years the first season was uh
record to edit and then the second
season was live and when we went live
that's when it got real it was a lot of
stress like people don't understand how
much work goes into all these
entertainment projects it's a lot of
time a lot of money and a lot of sweat
so tell me a little bit about your
family now um you've been in a
relationship for quite some time um with
your significant other that you love
dearly now I you know it it's really
tough because I've been in situations
where I was an entrepreneur and you know
and was in a relationship but you know
women are not not necessarily supportive
especially if they're working for
somebody else they're not really
thinking uh you know if they're just
working and you know and then you're
building a business and and sometimes
the business may not be producing any
money like how was your significant
other um you know like how how did you
guys you know kind of get this
relationship you know to a point where
you know that you you guys knew that you
had to support each
other honestly I've known Claudia since
1998 so she was there through my good
time and my bad throughout Junior High
in high school so she basically had an
understanding of who I was however when
we first started talking after 10 years
she's like you are completely different
from what you were in high school that's
because I had more of a confident
mindset and then Upon Us starting the
date she realized that I was very
ambitious and very passionate and I told
her I was like these are the situations
that I'm building myself towards and
these are this is the goal I want this
is the goal I have and I just I had a
very Stern approach where just just
telling her that my my children and my
passion and my businesses I'm trying to
build are my Forefront that my my my my
greatest focus and it was a tough
transition because I don't party I don't
drink I I don't really go out much to be
honest with you unless it's with my my
you know close friend Circle and with
the kids so it was definitely difficult
for her to adjust to but then she saw
just the mental and the spiritual
benefits of being an entrepreneur and
just being focused 1% on your passion
and I told her I was like the best way
to become the version of yourself the
best version of yourself is to just
pursue your passion 100% with no
distractions and you have to set those
boundaries and that's why you know
relationships with entrepreneurs are
difficult because we're stubborn like we
we we set our goal we go for and we
don't allow distractions to come in we
don't allow the typical societal
pressures to come in where we just we're
just focused and it's very difficult but
Claudia has been 1% supportive so of my
kids like my my son Jacob my daughter
Julie they understand that if I say
listen I'm just I got to do this one
task and then we'll spend another couple
hours together they get it because they
they understand the end result and I
love how my kids see my success because
it inspires them to understand that
whatever they have as a dream I'll be
there to support them to go through it
but they'll also have the the knowhow
and the passion to do it themselves as
well so basically long story short it
benefits my family but it took time for
them to see
how now now do you like it sounds all PE
peachy you know it sounds like roses I I
and I and I know with relationship it's
not always roses have you guys ever
thought about you know the direction
that that you were taking you know in
any of your interior of the journey and
how did you overcome that definitely
like whenever you cause someone to
change their thinking or to start
thinking a different way it causes a lot
of tension and we uh I just had to keep
in mind her that it's not a uh Netflix
it's not success instantly like it's
going to take time and I just need to
understand that that she believes in me
and there was times where I actually was
considering leaving the be heroes
Community behind and moving on to a
typical neto5 but what happened was
every time I did it I just got miserable
which affected our home life even more
because I brought that miserable
mentality home and she Claudia started
to realize that she started to realize
holy how Dave's taken out of his element
of creativity and his element of his
passion he's not a good version of
himself which is true so we had our
arguments but we knew that at the end of
the day it was not
worth um a devastating blow to our
relationship or ending our relationship
we understood that our love and our
unconditional love had to be put first
where she said you know what this is a
tough road we were financially dealing
with it for quite a while for the last
two years we've been not the best
situation financially however we just
just push through because she
understands the end result so we got we
we got some questions here uh not
questions but we have some comments um
uh so uh Christine Barry says being a
single parent and a successful business
owner it is also important to have
balance yeah and I I agree with you you
have to have balance like it's you know
I I don't I'm single you know what I
mean and you know yeah I date here and
there but I'm single and probably reason
there's a reason why because uh no one
woman no woman would put up with um the
the intense work ethic that I personally
have um you know um but you know not not
I'm not saying that no woman it's just
that I haven't found that person um that
would put up with that work ethic
because it it I'm sacrificing pretty
much everything my whole life um you
know to ensure that I become successful
but you also I do now like I have a
relationship with myself and I need me
time you know I I do need downtime I do
need to do stuff for my son I can't you
know I I can't sacrifice life for my son
I have to make sure that between the two
that it's okay but if I had three people
in the house it would I don't think I
would be as active because you know when
you care about the people in your life
you can't you can't just they they are
not there to just support your dreams
you know they have dreams
too oh definitely yeah and um Anna says
here's thank you for the link I can't
show up on the screen um it's a little
bit long but thanks for the link and uh
Anna uh she uh showed your your medium
link so thank you so much Anna for oh
thank you so much Anna that yeah that's
the be heroes Community medium page
which is has almost 100 articles on it
so a lot of good content so thanks for
sharing that yeah for sure and then um
zanadu says uh hold on hold on hold on
okay so Zan says Claudia sounds like a
true life partner it's awesome that you
have her in your corner Teamwork Makes
dreams work you know what um I I can't I
can't agree um anymore like I think that
um I think that we like people really
need to know and understand our dreams
and um the fact that you've been able to
you know to get your family on your side
and to get a lot of community support I
mean you're pretty in infectious I think
that a lot of people when they hear what
what you're all about um you know they
definitely want to support you now um I
want to before we get into our second
line of questioning uh Dave tell us a
little bit about your um you know
ADHD and you know I don't know if you're
dyslexic like myself but I know that you
had some struggles um with with uh with
a learning disability or or I don't know
if it was learning disability was it
ADHD that you had um it's mixture of
both they actually used to call it a
learning disability now it's a mental
health disability or mental health
illness uh I was diagnosed in 1997 I was
never medicated nor was I ever
approached to become medicated I don't
believe um like there's different levels
ADD and ADHD are very popular
conversations among social media right
now there's a lot of people that believe
it's not real a lot of people that
understand it is real there's a lot of
different conversations about it and I
always tell people the best conversation
to have is with someone who has it or
someone who has been diagnosed with it
but now they're trying to figure out if
it's actually real or not um it was a
tough struggle in school of course
because um in school it was very this is
how you learn or you don't learn at all
so there was times where I was
constantly sent to the office because I
was just you know air quote disruptive
uh air quote rude or had an add to
problem of course I did like I had my
own certain way of learning and when I
would try to do it I was disciplined for
like for one example and I think Claud
remember this I was in high school I got
the math question right but because I
didn't do it the way that they taught me
they felt it was worthy of being
disciplined and sent to the office for
and I was also held back in ECS because
of it um I wasn't diagnosed till 97
which I was in grade seven I was
diagnosed so for six years I was called
lazy unmotivated easily distracted
unable to focus a Class Clown and so
much more and then when I got diagnosed
it was like they finally realized holy
cow they need needs actual support and
yeah it led to a lot of struggles but at
the end of the day though I'm proud to
have it I will I refer to it as
disability as in th ability because this
ability gives me so much ability and
power to get everything that I dream
done I have a friend that I've I've
worked with uh for for quite some time
named Michael De haes and you know he
has cereal policy and he started a
movement that we are uh hustle zone is
going to be a part of but we we're
saying that we're we're no longer
calling disability disability we're
calling it um challenges because
everybody has challenges and if you if
you don't have a challenge then you
ought to have one because that's the
only way that you're going to grow and
be better and you know and dyslexia and
ADHD or add because I know I got a lot
of that um it's an ability for me and
but it's it's actually superpower
because all this you see the hustle Zone
that
creativity um is manifestation of way my
brain thinks you know so you kind of
have to use your brain in a different
way in order for you to like you know
we're just made differently no one said
that hey we had to sit in the classroom
and sit and listen and and um and and
write down notes and then we would get
it you know everyone learns differently
and you know they look at life
differently and and you know dyslexia
for example is a great ability um and
that's you know a lot of um um lot of
great entrepreneurs were dyslexic
because they say they see the world in a
completely different way so you know the
fact that you able to kind of manifest
it in your own way and I know this
because I know you're writing you you
can't stop writing like you you put your
energy in in your writing and again like
that's a natural that's a natural gift
because in my brain I don't want to
write because of my dyslexia um I don't
even want to touch it I don't even want
to look at it and then here you are just
like typing away because that's the way
that you utilize your um your your
gifts yeah like uh one of the biggest
faults that we have in our society
nowadays is people tend to focus on
their weaknesses more than Bing on their
strengths like I realize my weaknesses
and I don't go anywhere near them like I
probably people are like well you should
go near your weaknesses so you can help
build them into your strength no like
because that's time loss of being great
at what I'm good at I love writing it's
my favorite style of sharing and
speaking and I do video here and there
but I prefer writing the most so
therefore I focus on that the most so
that way I don't get rusty with it uh
you know one of my best piece of advice
I gave my my son and daughter is just
focus on your strength you know be great
at what you're good at and then when you
have time to focus on weakness if you
wish focus on it but our society is so
reversed and it's terrible how people
you know focus on their weaknesses and
at the same time ignore their strengths
as you know it's a matter of trying to
appeal and to impress to you know Susan
and Joe your neighbors and so much more
like people are so invested in trying to
impress other people that in reality
they're actually being counterproductive
towards their their future and they're
you know become their own
sabotage so what would you have said to
yourself um you know if you could go
back in time and talk to your old self
what would you tell it tell your old
self to be kind to myself because I beat
myself up so bad and I feel that that's
one of the reasons why I was so
vulnerable to being bullied and attacked
because myself I was just my internal
voice was so weakened so depressed so
negative that of course my external
voices would you know understand that
and per you know take part to it I would
be more kind to myself and realize that
listen like I had a lot of struggles
with my Mom leaving when I was four
years old and then cel's 18 being you
know dealing with ADHD and not being
diagnosed or getting any support for six
years like I was going through a lot and
to be quite honest with you the damage
that other people were doing to me was
not as damaging as what I was doing to
myself yeah yeah yeah I I agree with you
with that like uh the the the the fact
that you know a lot of a lot of a lot of
the reason why we suffer we suffer
because of internal um you know in the
internal struggle with ourselves because
especially when you're being bullied or
you're being put in situations where you
you don't want to be in um having that
struggle um to love yourself because you
you the first thing you ask yourself is
like why
me you know why me but you know you know
as an
entrepreneur um you know that you can't
only so far you could get with with that
that that attitude and that ideology you
kind of have to say yeah why me because
I'm the best you know why me because I'm
great you know why me because I'm going
to do I'm not going to let people hold
me back
right and um you know tell us a little
bit about entrepreneurship before before
we go into our next uh you know what
does entrepreneurship mean to you oh man
like I've noticed there's so many
different uh descriptions and
explanations for auralism and for me
it's just being free to to focus on what
you love to do and making your passion
your ability to make money like that's
what it is to me is just it's following
your passion and making that passion as
your your s of income 1% like you're
you're not doing it to benefit someone
else's dream because you know
fortunately I'm a I'm a part-time
entrepreneur to be honest like I still
have a full-time job with with the
Stampede here in Calgary but I realized
that in order to become a full-fledged
entrepreneur you got to have that
Foundation of finances first so it's
it's definitely a risk it's definitely
scary but the way I see it is people are
taking the risk of not being able to
retire till they're 65 and the average
lifespan in North America is 73 years
old so when so when you retired from
65 there's no guarantee how much longer
you have to live and if you're willing
to take that risk to work for someone
else and to build someone else's dreams
for the next 40 to 50 plus years you you
should be able to take that risk to
chase Your Passion because like my
number one my number one quote is making
passion your purpose it makes you the
best version of who you are 100% and
being entrepreneur is you've chosen to
make passion your
purpose uh so we got some we got some
comments in the uh I see there's a lot
of discussion I love it a lot of
discussion with this video which is
great so uh Christine Barry says Ryan
you stated that some women do not
understand or support when a husband
decides to become an entrepreneur this
is also be Um this can also be reserved
where the husband is not supportive and
threatened by women um being or the
reverse sorry you know dyslexia haha um
but this is this can be reversed where
the husband is not supportive and
threatened by oh yeah I mean you know it
is um that was the one thing that I
pride myself with my ex is that she's a
professional um she's a a a professional
dancer and you know certain type people
are like oh what kind of dancing what's
she doing no she's a professional dancer
works for um very prestigious uh dance
um um you know company here in Calgary
but she I always supported her because
you know I think we you know like I'm
I'm about movement and and in empowering
people to move forward and and uh you
know but I've seen relationships where
you know the husbands and the men you
know weren't supportive because they
seen seen their their you know their
spouse rise up and it can be very
humbling as a man to to know that your
woman is making more money than you or
has a more you know has a a better
career
you know but you know if that's what
you're focused on then you shouldn't be
in a relationship anyways because you
know you're kind of living together as
one as a unit as long as there's money
coming through like what do you think
Dave oh honestly it's a matter of Pride
I had a you know Pride can make you it
can break you and it broke me for so
many years because I had that that
stupidity of I had to be the bread
winner I had to do everything and it
comes down to the fact that if you're in
a relationship money shouldn't even be
your focus it should be part of your
life but not your focus it should be
building that life together so there's a
bit there actually was a time where
Claudia was making more money to me for
about two to three years because I was
so focused on just building towards VI
Heroes and so much more and I looked at
that as a partnership she was helping me
take care of the family and taking care
of our business and so much more and as
soon as you have someone that starts
looking down on you for being successful
that's definitely a red flag yeah
definitely 1% a red flag yeah yeah yeah
so uh we're going to go into our second
line of questioning uh cuz we're going
to be closing this uh these this uh
awesome conversation out but um I'm
going to have the camera on you and I
want to ask uh I want to ask you a few
questions here so this is our lightning
round uh for the hustle zone so what's
your favorite
dessert
cheesecake okay and um that's awesome
because I love cheesecake but I I can't
eat it because I'm vegan
um I even tried I I I I tried the the
vegan um cheesecake and it's disgusting
so you know yeah it's just to leave
behind Okay so next uh next uh lightning
round question here is texting or
talking oh
geez uh benefits of both but I prefer
talking okay uh favorite day of the
week Sunday favorite city in the us
besides the one you live or no sorry
favorite place in Canada besides the one
you live
in oh I'm GNA say Vancouver Island
Vancouver Island okay nickname of your
parents um nickname your parents used to
call
you uh my dad would always call me
champer son okay long song The the last
song that you
downloaded oh geez um In the Air Tonight
by
Nonpoint awesome
favorite
holiday
Christmas okay um fill in the blank
Taylor Swift
is trending is trending yeah um at what
age did you want to
retire 35 was the goal 35 how old are
you now 31 nowhere near you got four
year Well if if if if someone could do
it at age 17 I'm sure you could
exactly my motivation in invisibility or
super
strength super strength okay and what is
wrong uh is it wrong for a vegetarian to
eat animal
[Music]
crackers no okay awesome so Dave thank
you so much for participating at the
hustle Zone I really appreciate it um uh
you spending your time with me today uh
so Dave Let's uh um let's end this with
the traditional um hustle Zone call and
response so the pretty much the way that
um um it works is that I'll say welcome
to the and then you need to scream
hustle Zone as loud as you can so um I'm
going to say welcome to the hustle Zone
hustle Zone okay you're yelling with me
yeah no I'm not I'm just giving you an
example all right so all right all right
we're going to go cuz some people are
like I'm like welcome to the and they're
like welcome to the no you gotta say the
oh okay so welcome to the hustle Zone
awesome thank you so much for uh uh yeah
because I used to do Dave was just
mentioning to me that I used to do
the and like I don't know I was doing
that like even sorry even even when you
like even when you uh uh listen to
hustles Al you know it was I was
actually uh when I was dating someone I
was making fun of the situation I was
putting it on camera and I was making
light because we were hustling and I was
like well go to the power Zone and you
know for me I anyone that knows me I
like to kid around all the time so you
know it just became a thing but I'm like
I'm not going to do that anymore because
the Hy the hushy zone is a little bit
more sophisticated than that so um but
either way it was nice um nice to have
Dave as a guest uh Dave if you want to
um um stand by here and then I'll talk
to you I'll talk to you later but uh
thank you so much Dave for coming in and
I do appreciate um you know all the
service that you you're doing for the
Youth so thank you so much thank you for
having me always a pleasure so yeah
anyway uh that was a great interview
wasn't it and um you know it it seems
like Dave is um starting to uh catch
wind in his sale you know he's starting
to he's starting to um get to the the
place where he where he wants to be so
I'm very proud to be his friend and and
um you know seeing all the things um
that he's doing so thanks again Dave uh
folks we're going to continue to give
you guys the best content but we do need
your help um make sure you guys head
over to
GoFundMe um oops I'm I'm telling you why
here uh hold on go to
gofundme.com
hustle zoney TV and uh I do have one one
request uh for you guys uh we have I
have a friend that is uh one of the best
entrepreneurs that I know um and she is
into um she's into grinding and and and
really putting putting out her her work
and and um you know and I and I admire
her her strength and and I admire her
entrepreneurship however you know she is
caught into some you know Financial
Times so um and and I'm asking everybody
in the community to you know uh she has
the gok fund me I didn't get a chance to
load it up up on this page but you guys
can go to my personal Facebook page um
and see um you know and you'll see that
there will be an ad there for a GoFundMe
I'm not going to mention anything right
now I just want you guys just go to my
page you'll see a GoFundMe um requesting
um you know um requesting help because
you know some some of us entrepreneurs
sometimes when money doesn't come
through it really stifles us and really
puts us in a situation where we can't
um where we can't
Thrive and uh you know I I even been in
this business I've been in that
situation a lot of times uh where you
know cash flow people don't pay their
bills and then I'm stuck in the
financial bind um so I I definitely want
to help her out um I'm not putting
anything up on the screen yet because I
didn't have it prepared but you'll start
seeing me promote it um um you know in
the future and I'm going to talk to her
um to see if it's okay for me to mention
in all my lives but you guys can
definitely go to my um Facebook page
you'll see you'll see it there you'll
see the ad there um just click on it and
if you whatever you can donate $10 $25
you know to help her and her son uh cuz
currently right now she's homeless but I
know she's a hell of a entrepreneur
there's not uh you know she's someone
that I would um I know she's going to be
really successful but sometimes we all
need a boost so I'm going to use my
platform um to help her out out and um
like I said go to my Facebook page I'm
going to talk to her to see if I can
broadcast her story you know I want to
get her permission first before I do it
uh but you know I have a very
interesting way you you guys can just go
on to my page you know that's an
indirect way of promoting her without
putting her business out there um so
thank you guys all so much for for
participating in today's hustle Zone and
uh like I said make sure you guys check
us out on GoFundMe u.com and this
broadcast was brought to you by botak
creative we do more than just websites
we do more we do more we do more we
achieve more um you know we help others
achieve more uh it's we have a campaign
called the plus more that's why you see
the pluses in all of our logos because
uh we just want to give people the
ability to build online businesses you
know not just websites but online
businesses so please check us out and uh
my name is Ryan Perez thank you guys for
participating in the hustle Zone and I
will talk to you guys later
[Music]